One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
The Hunter
It's the mirage from earlier.
In the end, you've only got one body.
That's right. One of them is the real me.
The other four are illusions formed from reflections in the frigid air.
Illusions, you say?
That sounds mysterious and lovely.
But when you think about it rationally,
illusions obviously don't have offensive power.
In other words, this is just an empty threat.
That's right.
So you turn defiant? You're not sweet, at all.
Thunder Charge!
Only one of these five is real.
So what?
And...
Thunder Ball!
Only 20% of my attacks are real as well.
Why don't you try dodging them?
Oh, shoot! I have to defend myself!
Which ones are real?!
Their power, on the other hand, is 100%.
This is very different from the old Clima-Tact.
A mere Thunder Ball attack
has this much power.
With my next powerful attack, you're done.
What kind of prediction is that? How cocky!
It's not a prediction. It's a forecast.
I control both the humidity and temperature.
The weather in this room belongs to me!
What's the big deal with
controlling the weather?
The Six Powers are techniques
that exceed human abilities.
How insolent!
That wasn't the real one!
Today, the chance of finding the real me is still 20%.
While atmospheric pressure is stable, today's skies show signs...
of a stationary front of small, dark clouds and violent winds.
Given time, a clap of thunder should signal the lightning that will pierce your chest.
Beware of cardiac arrest!
Dark Cloud Tempo!
If this is lightning, I showed you earlier that I can guard myself.
As long as I'm being careful...
The flaw in that technique is that
you can't move around while using it.
You sure take me lightly. Are you
telling me to break it with an attack?!
Then...
Soap Sheep!
I don't have to know which one is the real one.
I'll swallow everything with a
big wave of Relaxing Bubbles.
Sheep Cloud!
Tidal Wave!
I'll be a goner if I get hit by that.
The one on the floor after I
swallow everything is the real one.
That's not gonna happen!
Cyclone Tempo!
She used wind to blow the bubbles away!
But it looks like the one who got
through it is the real one, huh?
Finger Pistol!
Oh? I thought it was another illusion.
I won't let you get away again.
I'll just riddle your body with holes.
You've already forgotten it, haven't you?
You should pay attention to
a navigator's weather forecast.
A thunderbolt will surge out...
from the dark clouds to the Clima-Tact!
Come on!
The clouds from earlier!
Thunder Lance Tempo!
No matter how strong you are,
my forecasts are never wrong.
My friends are waiting. I'll be taking your key.
Deer-gorilla! Where'd you go?!
What? Franky! What are you doing there?!
Oh, hey, lady.
That monster deer-gorilla in
your group came here, didn't he?
Deer... You mean Chopper?
Yeah, that deer-gorilla.
Yeah, he did. What's the deal?
What happened to him?
How should I know?! That was my question!
Isn't he someone who can transform like that?
How would I know?!
I've never seen him in that form.
I see. I thought you guys
might know how to deal with that.
Then, I guess I'll just kill him.
If you say that again, I'm gonna kill you.
I-I'll never say it again. Ever again.
By the way, you're not bad yourself.
You took this woman down?
Her key is important: the No. 2 key.
The key! Hold on a sec. I was just looking for it.
Key! Key! Where'd you hide it?
Yow! Nice scandalous behavior!
What the hell is this monster?!
Was there someone else with a zoan-type ability?!
Does that mean that this
guy's also part of CP9?!
Come to think of it, I feel
like I've seen him before.
Ch-Chopper?!
What're you doing, Chopper?! It's us!
Ahh! Stop it!
Hey, is that really Chopper?!
How come he doesn't recognize us?!
I don't know, but it must be Chopper!
Who else has those antlers and wears that hat?!
So, where's our only chance? Where's the No. 2 key?!
Who knows? This is it! We're gonna die.
But something is wrong.
Isn't he the one who looks
like he is about to die?
It seems as if his life force is rapidly fading.
Wh-Wh-What does that mean?
It may be that him staying in that form
uses up too much energy or something.
What the hell?! What do we do
about him and the other two?!
Hey, what happened to the key?
Where's the No. 2 key?!
I don't know what happened,
but he must've fought incredibly hard...
So hard that he transformed into that.
No. 2...
That's quite the interruption. What's that monster?
The buster call is imminent.
Of course he'd interrupt us.
It seems like he's one of those pirates.
Anything that gets in our way...
Should be eliminated.
Although he's insignificant...
We've got more prey.
Dammit! They're gonna attack Chopper!
Straighten your back,
named blade Nose Storm.
H-Hey! What're you gonna do?!
36-Pound Phoenix!
You bastard!
Step aside, you guys!
– Huh?
– That guy...!
Franky! What're you trying to do?!
This is one of our...
I know! Just be quiet.
This is the only way that I
can think of to deal with him.
Everyone with devil fruit powers has a weakness.
I'll push him out to sea.
I'll go easy, so bear with me!
Coup de...
Vent!
You bastard, Franky! That's reckless!
What're you doing to our friend?!
Don't worry. He discussed
this with me beforehand.
What?
What're they doing, attacking their own?
They sure do make a big fuss.
So you're finally free?
You'd better stop smiling and start regretting.
Never again...
will you get a chance to kill me like the one you just had,
World Government!
Battleships are preparing their attack!
Get off of Enies Lobby!
They're gonna start firing cannons!
Everyone, get off of the island!
We'll get dragged into the buster call!
We'll die if we stay here!
Stop, Nico Robin!
Even if you go back the way we came,
all you'll find are the corpses of pirates!
Enough already.
Teach her a lesson, Funkfreed!
Luffy is just ahead.
Don't hit her vital spots, got that?
Ivory...
Dart!
I won't let you escape, you dumb woman!
Don't underestimate me!
Now, let's go through the
door to our dreams.
He's back to normal.
He'd better not be dead.
I didn't expect that even his friends
wouldn't know how to handle that.
Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
I do!
Well, anyway, the fact remains
that he took out a member of CP9.
In consideration of your friends who
defended you even after you turned...
into such a terrible form,
I'll forgive you for attacking me.
We'd better hurry.
But... even if I hurry, I still don't know
how to get to the Gates of Justice.
We'll be your guides!
Little ones!
I found Franky!
What?! You guys know where the
passage to the Gates of Justice is?!
Yep, we do! We're here to be guides!
Grandma's over there, too.
Tell me where it is right away!
And I'll give you and old hag Kokoro
instructions as to what you should do!
Roger.
He's unconscious, but seems to be okay.
Oh, no! I have to bring the keys
to Nico Robin as soon as possible!
You guys bring that deer when you come in a bit!
– Okay.
– Got it! Go, Franky!
So, we have no choice but
to do that to stop Chopper.
And then, after that, take these
No. 3 and No. 4 keys and hurry to Robin.
One of them might unlock her handcuffs.
If so, call me using this portable
transponder snail that secretary had.
Okay.
Leave freeing Zoro and Noseking to me.
That's fine, but what will we do after that?
We've come this far, but even if
we're able to rescue Nico Robin,
there's still no bridge between this tower
and Enies Lobby. So we can't go back.
Yeah.
Now that a buster call has been sounded,
we don't have time to go back
the way we came in the first place.
So?
So there's no question about it, right?
Behind us is a deadly waterfall.
Ahead of us is a mysterious path.
Which would you pick?
Well, I guess that ahead is the only way.
Then, when we're done with
what we have to do here,
we'll all gather at the Gates of Justice!
As for what's after that, just leave it to...
– To you?!
– To luck!
Luck?!
We've...
Wasted quite a bit of time.
Damn straight!
I can't believe you guys have been
acting so dumb during an ordeal like this!
That's because this guy was doing stupid stuff.
You both are brainless!
Hurry up and get their keys already!
Tempest Kick:
Wire!
That's just as I instructed. Nice job, Zoro-kun!
Fight! Zoro!
You guys fight, too!
That long neck of yours...
You'd better hope it doesn't
become your weak point.
No need to worry about that.
I gained muscles that are strong enough
to give me full control of my neck.
And they've got the power of bullets, too!
Nose Pistol!
Wh-What the heck?
How can we feel this much impact from here?!
His nose made a square-shaped hole in that rock!
That nose is more amazing than Sogepp's!
Wh-Wh-Who're you calling Sogepp?!
And don't make needless
comparisons like that!
Well, at any rate...
Kaku's gotten quite
proficient at using his powers.
W-Wolf! I-I'm your adversary!
Hm? Don't get so worked up.
You guys wanna save your friend, right?
Th-That's right! I'll take your key!
Hm?
Huh?
Hurry up and take it to her.
What?
Go save Nico Robin.
Wh-What on earth are you...
To be honest, I don't wanna
kill people. I hate blood.
Hm?
Th-Then, I'll just...
take the key and...
No! Watch out!
Ten Finger Pistol!
Don't let your guard down.
I'm a wolf. I put people off
their guard then go for the throat.
Usopp!
D-Dammit! What am I doing?
What an unbelievable masked idiot!
Why don't you just run
around like you did earlier?
You're fast as lightning
when you're running away.
Stop mocking me.
Huh?
We no longer have that kind of time.
Advanced Kabuto!
Lethal Sunflower Star!
Oh?
Oh, I see. Fireworks, huh?
Usopp!
Moon Walk!
Stop it!
As I promised, your death will be instantaneous and without pain.
Too bad. If you'd stayed connected with
that shepherd and had him protect you,
you would've been okay.
You see what happens when a
lamb wanders off all by himself?
He gets eaten by a scary wolf.
Now, this is it for you!
Hey, stop it, wolf! You bastard!
Don't kill him! Please! We don't need your key!
You fool! You'll die next!
Tempest Kick!
Dammit!
Now, die!
Usopp!
Who the hell are you?!
The hunter.